endlessborland@gmail.com

Phone: 949-501-2160

Tustin, CA 92782

Skills

- · Java, Groovy
- Jira, Confluence, Bitbucket
- · Maven, Gradle
- Openshift, k8s, docker
- Jenkins, ansible, terraform, helm
- Git, GitLab CI, bash, Linux
- SQL, Networks, AWS
- C, C++, C
- Time Management and Organization
- Continuous Integration Systems
- Requirements Gathering and Analysis

Education And Training

05/2021

Bachelor of Science:

Software Engineering

Russian Technological University (MIREA)

Moscow

Languages

Russian:

Native/ Bilingual

English:

Native/ Bilingual

Web

- https://www.linkedin.com/in/e ndlessborland/
- https://github.com/endlessborl and

Denis Skorobogatov

Summary

DevOps engineer with 3 years proven success record in Russia's largest banking ecosystem, 6 years overall IT experience. Efficient individual contributor with experience of leading small engineering teams. Excelled at automation, standardization and technical support. Geared towards building versatile, transparent and user-friendly solutions. Key strengths include fast learning, strong communication skills and strategic planning.

Experience

SberBank Technologies, JSC - DevOps Team Lead (Remote)

Moscow, Russia

01/2022 - Current

- R&D introduced HELM to platform's deploy pipeline.
- Onboarded and trained new hires, 2 new team members successfully passed trial period.
- Third line technical support, 50+ applications migrated onto new platform.
- Provided technology-related details in easy-to-understand terms to management and personnel.

SberBank Technologies, JSC - DevOps Engineer

Moscow, Russia

11/2020 - 01/2022

- Developed internal standard for applications' configuration.
- Created an automated system to more efficiently verify app's configuration.
- Developed best practices guidelines for SberBank's proprietary cloud platform.
- Instructed Dev and Ops teams on new systems and software, such as terraform, jinja, etc., via presentation and provision of training materials.

SberBank Technologies, JSC - Junior DevOps Engineer

Moscow, Russia

08/2019 - 11/2020

- Refactored Istio configuration deploy to openshift/k8s clusters from bash to Groovy (Jenkins Scripted Pipeline)
- Migrated application deploy to openshift/k8s clusters from bash to Groovy (Jenkins Scripted Pipeline)
- Decreased deploy time by 30%

MD Assistance, Co, LLC - IT Specialist

Moscow, Russia 09/2016 - 08/2019

- Performed IT technical support
- Automated epicrisis delivery for translation services and to insurance companies
- · Optimized database requests

Cybernated Forge LLC - System administrator

Moscow, Russia 04/2016 - 09/2016

• Maintained hardware/software/network - up to 25 machines